Looking deeply inside nature,
译者：Amer Da'our审计员：Mhd Adnan Ayasso
through the magnifying glass of science,
深入自然
designers extract principles,
processes and materials
从科学的角度
that are forming the very basis
of design methodology.
设计师提取原则
From synthetic constructs
that resemble biological materials,
工艺与材料
to computational methods
that emulate neural processes,
构成设计方法的基础
nature is driving design.
相似的合成配方
Design is also driving nature.
生物材料
In realms of genetics, regenerative
medicine and synthetic biology,
匹配神经操作的计算系统
designers are growing novel technologies,
自然引领设计
not foreseen or anticipated by nature.
设计也指导自然
Bionics explores the interplay
between biology and design.
在遗传学，再生医学领域
As you can see, my legs are bionic.
和合成生物学
Today, I will tell human stories
of bionic integration;
设计师正在开发新技术
how electromechanics attached
to the body, and implanted inside the body
天生没有预料或预期
are beginning to bridge the gap
between disability and ability,
生物医学工程正在研究相互作用
between human limitation
and human potential.
在生物学与设计之间
Bionics has defined my physicality.
如您所见，我的腿很工业
In 1982, both of my legs were amputated
今天我要讲人类的故事
due to tissue damage from frostbite,
关于电子合并
incurred during
a mountain-climbing accident.
电子与人体的关系
At that time, I didn't
view my body as broken.
植入体内
I reasoned that a human being
can never be "broken."
它正在弥合差距
Technology is broken.
在无能与力量之间
Technology is inadequate.
在人的能力有限之间
This simple but powerful idea
was a call to arms,
和人类的潜力
to advance technology
for the elimination of my own disability,
生物电子学决定了我的身体能力
and ultimately, the disability of others.
1982年，我的腿被截肢
I began by developing specialized limbs
因为组织被霜冻损坏
that allowed me to return
to the vertical world
我有一次登山事故
of rock and ice climbing.
当时我没有看着我的身体
I quickly realized that the artificial
part of my body is malleable;
作为清障车
able to take on any form, any function --
我的结论是，人类
a blank slate for which to create,
它永远不会被摧毁
perhaps, structures that could extend
beyond biological capability.
技术下降
I made my height adjustable.
技术不合适
I could be as short as five feet
or as tall as I'd like.
这个想法很简单但是很强大
(Laughter)
这是一个邀请
So when I was feeling bad about myself,
诱导技术
insecure, I would jack my height up.
取消我的骨
(Laughter)
最后，其他人无能为力
But when I was feeling
confident and suave,
我开始发展专业派对
I would knock my height down a notch,
just to give the competition a chance.
它让我回来了
(Laughter)
到攀登石头和雪的垂直世界
(Applause)
我很快意识到假器官在我体内
Narrow-edged feet allowed me
to climb steep rock fissures,
灵活
where the human foot cannot penetrate,
它可以具有任何形状和功能
and spiked feet enabled me
to climb vertical ice walls,
作为可以制作的白页
without ever experiencing
muscle leg fatigue.
可以扩展的结构
Through technological innovation,
生物能力
I returned to my sport,
stronger and better.
它使我的身高可调
Technology had eliminated my disability,
我的年龄可以短到五英尺，也可以长到我喜欢的时间
and allowed me a new climbing prowess.
（笑声）
As a young man, I imagined a future world
where technology so advanced
当我为自己感到难过时
could rid the world of disability,
或缺乏信心，我会增加身高
a world in which neural
implants would allow
但是当我感到自信和说服时
the visually impaired to see.
稍微降低我的身高
A world in which the paralyzed
could walk, via body exoskeletons.
只是给竞争对手一个机会
Sadly, because of
deficiencies in technology,
（笑声）（掌声）
disability is rampant in the world.
纤细的楔形脚使我能够攀爬
This gentleman is missing three limbs.
陡峭的骨折
As a testimony to current technology,
he is out of the wheelchair,
人脚很难穿透
but we need to do a better job in bionics,
to allow, one day, full rehabilitation
带刺的脚使我得以攀爬
for a person with this level of injury.
垂直冰墙
At the MIT Media Lab, we've established
the Center for Extreme Bionics.
没有肌肉疲劳
The mission of the center
is to put forth fundamental science
通过技术创新，
and technological capability
我回到自己的运动中越来越强
that will allow the biomechatronic
and regenerative repair of humans,
科技消除了我的ac骨
across a broad range
of brain and body disabilities.
它给了我新的攀登能力
Today, I'm going to tell you
how my legs function, how they work,
作为一个年轻人，我设想了一个未来世界
as a case in point for this center.
技术非常复杂
Now, I made sure to shave
my legs last night,
从而摆脱阳imp的世界
because I knew I'd be showing them off.
允许神经植入的世界
(Laughter)
对于视力障碍者
Bionics entails the engineering
of extreme interfaces.
瘫痪者可以行走的世界
There's three extreme
interfaces in my bionic limbs:
通过外部结构
mechanical, how my limbs
are attached to my biological body;
不幸的是，由于缺乏技术
dynamic, how they move
like flesh and bone;
世界赤字猖ramp
and electrical, how they communicate
with my nervous system.
这个大师有四肢
I'll begin with mechanical interface.
作为对当前技术的证明
In the area of design,
we still do not understand
他从轮椅上站起来
how to attach devices
to the body mechanically.
但是我们需要在生物电子学上做出更大的努力
It's extraordinary to me
that in this day and age,
让一天完全康复
one of the most mature,
oldest technologies
对于如此受伤的人
in the human timeline, the shoe,
still gives us blisters.
我们位于麻省理工学院媒体实验室
How can this be?
极端生物电子学的枢纽
We have no idea how to attach
things to our bodies.
中心的使命
This is the beautifully
lyrical design work
是发展基础科学
of Professor Neri Oxman
at the MIT Media Lab,
技术能力将使
showing spatially varying
exoskeletal impedances,
用于人类的生物机电一体化和再生修复
shown here by color variation
in this 3D-printed model.
大规模
Imagine a future where clothing
is stiff and soft where you need it,
脑和身体残疾
when you need it, for optimal
support and flexibility,
今天我会告诉你如何操作我的腿
without ever causing discomfort.
以及如何运作
My bionic limbs are attached
to my biological body
我们在这个中心做的一个例子
via synthetic skins
with stiffness variations,
我昨晚一定要刮腿
that mirror my underlying
tissue biomechanics.
我知道我要给你看
To achieve that mirroring, we first
developed a mathematical model
仿生学需要独特的界面工程
of my biological limb.
我的电子终端中有三个独特的界面：
To that end, we used
imaging tools such as MRI,
机械接口，以及我的末端如何连接
to look inside my body,
用我的身体
to figure out the geometries
and locations of various tissues.
动态界面以及如何将其动态地移动
We also took robotic tools --
电子接口以及如何进行通讯
here's a 14-actuator circle
that goes around the biological limb.
随着我的神经系统
The actuators come in,
find the surface of the limb,
我将从机械接口开始
measure its unloaded shape,
在设计领域，我们还是不明白
and then they push on the tissues
如何将设备机械连接到人体
to measure tissue compliances
at each anatomical point.
今天不正常
We combine these imaging and robotic data
最成熟，最古老的技术之一
to build a mathematical description
of my biological limb, shown on the left.
在人类时代，这就是鞋子
You see a bunch of points, or nodes?
它仍然导致我们溃疡
At each node, there's a color
that represents tissue compliance.
怎么发生的？
We then do a mathematical transformation
to the design of the synthetic skin,
我们不知道事物如何附着在我们的身体上
shown on the right.
这是一件精美的作品
And we've discovered optimality is:
麻省理工学院实验室的Nery Oxman教授
where the body is stiff,
the synthetic skin should be soft,
显示各种外部结构成分
where the body is soft,
the synthetic skin is stiff,
在这里以不同的颜色显示
and this mirroring occurs
across all tissue compliances.
以这种3D打印形式
With this framework,
we've produced bionic limbs
想象一下衣服的未来
that are the most comfortable
limbs I've ever worn.
无论您需要什么，都可以用软硬
Clearly, in the future, our clothing,
our shoes, our braces, our prostheses,
当您需要完美的支持和灵活性时
will no longer be designed
and manufactured using artisan strategies,
完全不会造成不适
but rather, data-driven
quantitative frameworks.
我的电子器官连接到我的重要身体
In that future, our shoes
will no longer give us blisters.
由人造皮革制成
We're also embedding
sensing and smart materials
具有不同的刚度
into the synthetic skins.
那反映了我下层组织的生物力学
This is a material developed
by SRI International, California.
为了实现这种逆转
Under electrostatic effect,
it changes stiffness.
首先我们开发了一个算术模型
So under zero voltage,
the material is compliant,
对于我至关重要的聚会
it's floppy like paper.
为此，我们使用了MRI等成像工具
Then the button's pushed,
a voltage is applied,
让我们看看我的身体
and it becomes stiff as a board.
了解几何形状和位置
(Tapping sounds)
不同的组织
We embed this material
into the synthetic skin
我们还使用了机器人工具
that attaches my bionic limb
to my biological body.
这是14集的机械触发
When I walk here, it's no voltage.
围绕生命的终结
My interface is soft and compliant.
输入机械执行器并找到尖端的表面
The button's pushed,
voltage is applied, and it stiffens,
它测量其空心形式
offering me a greater maneuverability
over the bionic limb.
然后你去纸巾
We're also building exoskeletons.
测量组织相容性
This exoskeleton becomes stiff and soft
在每个解剖点
in just the right areas
of the running cycle,
我们收集这些机器人图像和信息
to protect the biological joints
from high impacts and degradation.
让我们建立一个算法
In the future, we'll all
be wearing exoskeletons
达到我至关重要的目标，如左图所示
in common activities, such as running.
您会看到一组点或节点
Next, dynamic interface.
在每个节点上都有代表组织相容性的颜色
How do my bionic limbs
move like flesh and bone?
然后我们进行帐户转帐
At my MIT lab, we study how humans
with normal physiologies
人造革设计
stand, walk and run.
如右图所示
What are the muscles doing,
我们发现理想是
and how are they controlled
by the spinal cord?
当身体结实时，人造革必须光滑
This basic science
motivates what we build.
当身体柔软时，人造革必须坚固
We're building bionic ankles,
knees and hips.
而这种逆转发生
We're building body parts
from the ground up.
通过符合所有组织
The bionic limbs that I'm wearing
are called BiOMs.
在这种情况下
They've been fitted
to nearly 1,000 patients,
我们制作了电子派对
400 of which have been
wounded U.S. soldiers.
这是最舒适的衣服
How does it work?
显然在未来
At heel strike, under computer control,
我们的衣服，鞋子和手镯
the system controls stiffness,
假肢不再设计
to attenuate the shock
of the limb hitting the ground.
它是使用工匠策略制作的
Then at mid-stance, the bionic limb
outputs high torques and powers
相反，数据推动了定量框架
to lift the person
into the walking stride,
在那个未来我们的鞋子
comparable to how muscles
work in the calf region.
再也不会引起起泡
This bionic propulsion is very important
clinically to patients.
我们还将传感器和智能材料相结合
So on the left, you see
the bionic device worn by a lady,
合成革
on the right, a passive device
worn by the same lady,
这种材料
that fails to emulate
normal muscle function,
由加利福尼亚州的斯坦福国际研究所开发
enabling her to do something
everyone should be able to do:
在电效应下，它会改变其硬度
go up and down their steps at home.
即使在零电压下，材料也不兼容
Bionics also allows
for extraordinary athletic feats.
像纸一样灵活
Here's a gentleman running
up a rocky pathway.
在按钮的压力下，施加电压
This is Steve Martin --
not the comedian --
像木板一样变硬
who lost his legs in a bomb blast
in Afghanistan.
我们将这些材料组合成人造革
We're also building exoskeletal
structures using these same principles,
将假肢连接到生物体
that wrap around the biological limb.
当你走到这里
This gentleman does not have
any leg condition, any disability.
没有有效电压
He has a normal physiology,
柔软且兼容的交互性
so these exoskeletons are applying
muscle-like torques and powers,
当按下按钮时，施加电压
so that his own muscles need not
apply those torques and powers.
然后变硬
This is the first exoskeleton in history
that actually augments human walking.
它为我提供了极大的可操作性
It significantly reduces metabolic cost.
在电子方面
It's so profound in its augmentation,
我们还建造外部结构
that when a normal, healthy person
wears the device for 40 minutes
这个外骨骼变得僵硬
and then takes it off,
仅在操作周期的正确区域
their own biological legs feel
ridiculously heavy and awkward.
为了保护生物关节
We're beginning the age in which
machines attached to our bodies
来自碰撞和割伤
will make us stronger
and faster and more efficient.
将来我们都会穿外部结构
Moving on to electrical interface:
在日常活动中，例如跑步
How do my bionic limbs communicate
with my nervous system?
接下来，动态界面
Across my residual limb are electrodes
我的电子四肢如何像骨肉一样运动？
that measure the electrical
pulse of my muscles.
在麻省理工学院媒体实验室，我们研究人类的行为
That's communicated to the bionic limb,
站立，散步和慢跑的博物学家
so when I think about moving
my phantom limb,
肌肉做什么
the robot tracks those movement desires.
脊髓如何控制它？
This diagram shows fundamentally
how the bionic limb is controlled.
基础科学支持建设过程
So we model the missing biological limb,
我们制造脚踝，膝盖和电子大腿
and we've discovered
what reflexes occurred,
我们还为整个身体打造四肢
how the reflexes of the spinal cord
are controlling the muscles.
我穿的四肢称为（BiOM）。
And that capability is embedded
in the chips of the bionic limb.
已为近1000位患者安装
What we've done, then, is we modulate
the sensitivity of the reflex,
其中有400个是为受伤的美国士兵安装的
the modeled spinal reflex,
with the neural signal,
如何运作？只要脚跟一脚掌就可以通过计算机进行控制
so when I relax my muscles
in my residual limb,
系统控制刚性
I get very little torque and power,
减少肢体撞击地面的影响
but the more I fire my muscles,
the more torque I get,
在手术过程中，四肢在抽水
and I can even run.
大功率高扭矩抬起人
And that was the first demonstration
of a running gait under neural command.
到台阶位置
Feels great.
后腿肌肉的运作方式
(Applause)
推动成员前进非常重要
We want to go a step further.
对于地面患者
We want to actually close the loop
在左侧，我们看到了电子终端
between the human
and the bionic external limb.
被女士磨损-在右侧
We're doing experiments
具有非智能派对的同一位女士
where we're growing nerves,
transected nerves,
它无法模拟自然肌肉的作用
through channels, or micro-channel arrays.
这门科学使她能够做某事
On the other side of the channel,
每个人都应该这样做
the nerve then attaches to cells,
它在房子的楼梯上下
skin cells and muscle cells.
这个标志也使我们的运动脚很棒
In the motor channels, we can sense
how the person wishes to move.
在这里，我们看到一个人在岩石路上奔跑
That can be sent out wirelessly
to the bionic limb,
这是史蒂夫·马丁，不是喜剧演员
then [sensory information]
on the bionic limb
谁因阿富汗爆炸案而失去双腿
can be converted to stimulations
in adjacent channels,
我们也在建造室外建筑
sensory channels.
使用相同的原则
So when this is fully developed
and for human use,
通过用外部结构包裹重要器官
persons like myself will not only have
这个男人没有受苦
synthetic limbs that move
like flesh and bone,
他的脚有任何受伤或残疾
but actually feel like flesh and bone.
他的身体状况完好无损
This video shows Lisa Mallette,
拥有这些结构
shortly after being fitted
with two bionic limbs.
旋转力和运动像天然肌肉
Indeed, bionics is making
a profound difference in people's lives.
他的肌肉不需要做的地方
(Video) Lisa Mallette: Oh my God.
有任何力或扭矩
LM: Oh my God, I can't believe it!
这是历史上第一个外部结构
(Video) (Laughter)
它模拟自然的人类行走
LM: It's just like I've got a real leg!
显着降低新陈代谢
Woman: Now, don't start running.
步行的发展量很大
Man: Now turn around,
and do the same thing walking up,
即使一个正常的人出现
but get on your heel to toe, like you
would normally just walk on level ground.
戴40分钟
Try to walk right up the hill.
然后脱掉
LM: Oh my God.
他觉得自己的脚是真实的
Man: Is it pushing you up?
沉重且极不平衡
LM: Yes! I'm not even --
I can't even describe it.
我们正处在时间的起点上
Man: It's pushing you right up.
它将使我们的机器连接到我们的身体
Hugh Herr: Next week,
I'm visiting the Center --
更快更强
Thank you. Thank you.
更有效
(Applause)
现在我们转向电气通信
Thank you.
我的四肢如何冒险
Next week I'm visiting the Center
for Medicare and Medicaid Services,
随着我的神经系统
and I'm going to try to convince CMS
在我腿的其余部分，我们看到了电极
to grant appropriate
code language and pricing,
它可以测量我的肌肉振动
so this technology can be made available
to the patients that need it.
这又会给机器人的两端带来风险
(Applause)
所以当我考虑移动它时
Thank you.
机器人应用您想到的动作
(Applause)
该图显示了原理
It's not well appreciated,
but over half of the world's population
如何控制此自动结束
suffers from some form of cognitive,
emotional, sensory or motor condition,
因此，我们应用缺少的自然肢体的运动
and because of poor technology,
too often, conditions result in disability
我们发现了发生的反应
and a poorer quality of life.
以及脊柱反应如何
Basic levels of physiological function
should be a part of our human rights.
控制肌肉
Every person should have the right
to live life without disability
而这种能力融合
if they so choose --
在电子端芯片中
the right to live life
without severe depression;
我们已经做的是类似的
the right to see a loved one,
in the case of seeing-impaired;
响应灵敏度
or the right to walk or to dance,
类似的骨架反应
in the case of limb paralysis
or limb amputation.
随着神经信号
As a society, we can
achieve these human rights,
当我放松脚的其余部分的肌肉时
if we accept the proposition
that humans are not disabled.
我有一点旋转和力量
A person can never be broken.
但是我越努力地工作
Our built environment, our technologies,
我旋转得更多
are broken and disabled.
我什至可以跑步
We the people need not
accept our limitations,
这是第一场演出
but can transcend disability
through technological innovation.
用于由紧张命令控制的跑步
Indeed, through fundamental advances
in bionics in this century,
感觉很棒
we will set the technological foundation
for an enhanced human experience,
（鼓掌）
and we will end disability.
我们要向前迈进
I'd like to finish up
with one more story, a beautiful story.
我们渴望弥合差距
The story of Adrianne Haslet-Davis.
在人类和重要机械肢体之间
Adrianne lost her left leg
in the Boston terrorist attack.
我们正在做实验，我们可以
I met Adrianne when this photo was taken,
at Spaulding Rehabilitation Hospital.
通过其移除植入物
Adrianne is a dancer, a ballroom dancer.
它以精致的车道形式穿过通道
Adrianne breathes and lives dance.
在频道的另一边
It is her expression. It is her art form.
神经与细胞沟通
Naturally, when she lost her limb
in the Boston terrorist attack,
皮肤细胞和肌肉细胞
she wanted to return to the dance floor.
通过这些渠道，我们可以感觉到
After meeting her
and driving home in my car,
一个人想参加的运动
I thought, I'm an MIT professor.
I have resources.
无线发送到自动化端
Let's build her a bionic limb,
然后可以将其转换
to enable her to go back
to her life of dance.
机器人末端的传感器可触及催化剂
I brought in MIT scientists
with expertise in prosthetics,
在相邻的感觉通道中
robotics, machine learning
and biomechanics,
因此，当所需的项目完成时
and over a 200-day research period,
we studied dance.
提供人类服务
We brought in dancers
with biological limbs,
像我这样的人不仅会喜欢它
and we studied how they move,
假肢像肉和骨头一样运动
what forces they apply on the dance floor,
相反，他们会感觉像他们的骨肉一样
and we took those data,
该视频显示了丽莎·马莱特
and we put forth
fundamental principles of dance,
获得两个自动成员后立即
reflexive dance capability,
其实这些目的是
and we embedded that intelligence
into the bionic limb.
人们生活的巨大变化
Bionics is not only about making
people stronger and faster.
（视频）丽莎·马莱特：哦，天哪
Our expression, our humanity
can be embedded into electromechanics.
天哪，我不敢相信
It was 3,5 seconds between the bomb blasts
in the Boston terrorist attack.
我觉得我有脚！
In 3,5 seconds, the criminals and cowards
took Adrianne off the dance floor.
我的脚不要开始跑步
In 200 days, we put her back.
男人：现在转身
We will not be intimidated, brought down,
diminished, conquered or stopped
做同样的，走
by acts of violence.
在脚后跟和前脚上走到母鹿
(Applause)
好像您在弯曲的表面上行走
Ladies and gentlemen, please allow me
to introduce Adrianne Haslet-Davis,
尝试上山
her first performance since the attack.
丽莎：天哪
She's dancing with Christian Lightner.
男人：你把你推高了吗
(Applause)
丽莎：是的！我不是...。我无法形容
(Music: "Ring My Bell"
performed by Enrique Iglesias)
男人：它推动了你
(Applause)
Hage Hair：下周我将前往购物中心
Ladies and gentlemen,
members of the research team:
（鼓掌）谢谢，谢谢
Elliott Rouse
谢谢，下周我会拜访
and Nathan Villagaray-Carski.
老年人和贫困者医疗中心
Elliott and Nathan.
我会说服中心
(Applause)
通过提供适当的名称和价格
为了使这项技术可用